

Dimitar Mitrevski

Date of birth: 25/01/2000

Nationality: Macedonian/citizen

of the Republic of North

Macedonia

Gender: Male

CONTACT

- s.Nakolec, Resen Resen 7318, North Macedonia (Home)
- dimitarmitrevski5@gmail.co
- (+389) 072642390
- https://bintern.com
- https://dimitar.rocks
- https://www.facebook.com/ dimitar.mitrevski4
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/ dimitar-mitrevski/
- https://www.instagram.com/ mitrevski4/
- https://github.com/ <u>DimitarMitrevski</u> (GitHub)
- +38972642390 (Viber)



ABOUT MF

I'm Dimitar Mitrevski a full-stack developer with over 4 years of working experience on different projects in the field of web development with international clients. I'm passionate about Information technology and I strongly believe that It's going to change the world for the better. Currently, I'm finishing my master's degree at the Faculty of Information and Communication Technologies in Bitola, Macedonia.

WORK EXPERIENCE

01/07/2023 - CURRENT Bitola, North Macedonia

Intermediate Technical Consultant IWConnect

As an Intermediate Technical Consultant, my responsibilities were:

- Development of Web applications
- · Delivering tasks on time
- Reviewing PRs from other colleagues

Technologies that I'm using at IWConnect are React.js, Redux.js, Material UI, React Query, D3.js, etc.
I have been working for two big internal products of the company

which have great potential.

27/10/2021 - 15/06/2023

Web Developer | Freelance UpWork

As a freelance Web Developer on UpWork, I've had the opportunity to work with different clients on a variety of projects that were challenging and interesting. I've gained a lot of experience in product development and communication with clients by turning their ideas into reality.

15/11/2022 - 25/05/2023 Bitola, North Macedonia

Teaching assistant Faculty of Information and Communication Technologies

As a teaching assistant at FICT, I am helping students learn about the practical application of the subjects.

am a teaching assistant for five different subjects, the subjects are System Software, Enterprise Information Systems, Web technologies, NoSQL databases, and Basics of Artificial Intelligence.

01/09/2019 - 30/06/2023 Bitola, North Macedonia

CEO & Founder / Web Developer Bintern

I have founded Bintern with a vision to help students around the world to become more and get the job they desire to work. My duties as a CEO and founder are a variety of tasks such as Web developer, Marketing agent, Sales representative, and decision-maker. I'm passionate about technology and startups and I see my startup as a potential global company such as Facebook, Amazon, Google and etc. From working in my startup I have gained a variety of skills that are helping me through my professional development.

10/02/2019 – 10/06/2019 Bitola, North Macedonia

Advertising copywriter Cosmic Development

My position was about creating content for marketing on a project that was a collaboration between the Faculty of information and communication technologies and Cosmic Development called "Profiles on social media from students for students". The project was about creating a non-formal profiles of our faculty on social media that was maintained by students. I was creating content for posts, blogs, stories and etc.

11/06/2019 - 11/10/2019 Bitola, North Macedonia

Online marketer Javen Advertajzing

I was an intern for online/digital marketing at Javen Advertajzing. My tasks were about promoting the company's products/services javen-agro and javen.mk. I was creating blogs and posts about the products and I was contacting potential costumers through social media. Also I was an admin of a facebook group that was about the javen-agro product and the main aim was connecting the farmers with potential costumers.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

25/10/2022 - CURRENT Bitola, North Macedonia

Master of Computer Science and Communications Engineering Faculty of Information and Communication Technologies

Address ul. Partizanska, bb, 7000, Bitola, North Macedonia Website https://fikt.uklo.edu.mk

01/10/2018 - 07/07/2022 Bitola, North Macedonia

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science and Communications Engineering (BSc CSCE) Faculty of Information and Communication Technologies

Address ul.Partiznska, bb, 7000, Bitola, North Macedonia | Website https://www.fikt.uklo.edu.mk

10/08/2018 - 20/08/2020 Bitola, North Macedonia

Lifeguard for open waters Red Cross - Macedonia

Address Filip II Makedonski 54, 7000, Bitola, North Macedonia | Website https://www.crvenkrst-bitola.org.mk/

LANGUAGE SKILLS

MOTHER TONGUE(S): Macedonian

Other language(s):

English

Listening C2Spoken production C1Reading C2Spoken interaction C1

German

Writing C1

Listening A2 Spoken production A2
Reading A2 Spoken interaction A2

Writing A2

Croatian

Listening C1Spoken production B2Reading B2Spoken interaction B2

Writing B2

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

DIGITAL SKILLS

WEB DEVELOPMENT TECHNOLOGIES

HTML5 | CSS3 | JavaScript | Vue.js | Nuxt.js | Bootstrap | PHP | TypeScript | Node.js | Express.js | D3.js | React.js | React Query | Redux.js | JQuery | Material Design - Material UI

SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT TOOLS

Git | GitHub | SCRUM | Postman | Trello | AWS Cloud | Linux | Jira | Google Cloud Platform | Algolia Search | Azure Cognitive Search

DATABASES AND DATA STRUCTURES

Firebase | MongoDB | NoSQL | SQL | MySQL | JSON | XML

OTHER DIGITAL TOOLS

Figma | WordPress | Canva | Microsoft Office

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Driving Licence

Driving Licence: AM
Driving Licence: B

Conferences and seminars

27/11/2019 - 27/11/2019 Bitola, Macedonia

Career fair 4 I was a speaker at this conference. My topic was "From student to entrepreneur" and I have shared my entrepreneurial journey. It was a great experience to speak in front of young people passionate to become leaders and successful people.

Projects

27/02/2020 - 09/03/2020

TC: Code Communication - Sofia, Bulgaria Erasmus+ training course in Sofia, Bulgaria called "Code Communication". In this training course I have learned about NLP, DISK communication model, and about different learning and presenting styles. I have improved my presenting skills and my public speaking. I have learned a lot and have great experiences.

03/02/2020 - 09/02/2020

TC: New Young Entrepreneurs - Skopje, Macedonia Erasmus+ training course called "New Young Entrepreneurs" about helping young people get employed through entrepreneurship and decreasing the unemployment rate in Europe. I have improved my entrepreneurship skills and connected with great entrepreneurs from the countries that have been a prat of this project.

04/08/2020 - 11/08/2020

YE: Youth Competences - Samobor, Croatia Erasmus+ youth exchange called "Youth Competences". This project was about helping unemployed people to require new skills that are going to help them to find a job. I have expanded my horizons and learned new ways to require the right skills so I will significantly increase my employment chances.

27/03/2021 - 04/04/2021

YE: Greenland - Samobor, Croatia Erasmus+ youth exchange called "Greenland was about contributing to the promotion of increasingly prominent social goals such as environmental protection, sustainable development, and healthy lifestyles, and on the other hand to create jobs and stimulate entrepreneurship. Throughout this project, I have learned about how to preserve nature, how to improve my lifestyle, and grow as an entrepreneur.

Management and leadership skills

Public speaking I have held workshops about business and personal development and growth. I have spoken on different events such as business presentations(pitching), Erasmus + projects, seminars and webinars.

Presentation skills I have some experience in presenting in front of audience a business idea, my self or educational content. I have gained my presentation skills by practice from doing presentations at faculty, business events and etc.

Hobbies and interests

Reading books I like to expand my knowledge. I like to read books about personal development and growth. From every book I gain knowledge that is priceless and it is serving me well. I have a interesting quote that I follow "The more I learn, the more I realize how much I don't know."- Albert Einstein.

Listening to music I enjoy listening to music. I don't have a certain type of music that I listen. When I'm listening to music it is giving me energy, peace and motivation to do things. I want to listen music spontaneously depending on my mood. I see art in every song that I listen and I enjoy it.

Communication and interpersonal skills

Emotional intelligence I'm learning about how to manage my emotions so I give to the world the best version of my self. I believe that discovering yourself is a lifetime journey.